Walter and Naomi Rosenblum Collection of Photography and Photographic History MSS.556
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Naomi Rosenblum's Research Materials, Correspondence, Subject Files, and Lectures, 1860-2018 (inclusive), 1963-2014 (bulk); 21.38 Linear Feet in 49 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 4 oversized flat boxes, and 1 flat file folder
  - Misc. Corr. Re: P.S. Projects, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Notes: NR Odds & Ends (Re: Strand), 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Mis Notes by NR handwritten re: PS, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Un Paese/Notes Re, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - P. STR/Interview/Milton Brown/WR/NR & NR, 1971, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Misc/Odds & Ends (Paul Strand), 2014 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - O'Keeffe + Strand Misc. Material, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - H&P Strand Archive Holdings, 1984, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Strand/Stieglitz Corr/Copies, 1926-1933 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - E Mc/Paul Strand Corr, Original + Copy, 1933-1934, 1936, 1960, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Handwritten Notes from NR/Conversations with P.S., 1973, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Handwritte Notes NR, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Corr Re: European Exhibition (of P.S.), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Camera Club, NY, Lecture on P.S. by NR, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Paul Strand Exhibition Catalog, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Talks NR/PS & HS/Dedication, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - FBI Papers/Paul Strand, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Strand/Aronson Corr, 1947, 1966, 1969, 1970-1978, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ernie O'Malley/Paul Strand, 1932, 1934, 1953-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Interview/PS/Zur Stockeggal, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Camera & Darkroom Magazine (Paul Strand), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Strand Aronson Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Aesthetics: Painting & Sculpture Photography, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Paul Str/Narrative Chronology, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Strand/Crucifixion, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Strand and Film: A Changing Sensibility (Naomi Rosenblum), 2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Paul Strand 16 Graveures, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Strand Conv. Photography Pictorialism/Photo-Secession, 1973, 1975, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Paul Strand/Whitney Mus, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Paul Strand Exhibition/National Gall of Art, 1976, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Rebecca James/ Paul Str./Corr + Exhibition Annance, 1933-1934, 1966, 1974, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Paul Str Colloquium/Getty Mus/Transcript, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Stra Colloq/Getty Prepatory, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Phila Mu/Paul Str Archive, 1993, 2010, 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Newhall/Strand, 1947-1972 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
  - Rebecca Str/Paul Str Corr., 1929-1931 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Zabriskie/Announcements/2 Talks/Typescripts, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Misc, Lists/Strand Photos, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Announcements/Assorted/Lists, 1972, 1977, 1985-1986, 1990-1991, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Matter Re: PS, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Articles by Paul Strand, 1917, 1921-1922, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - P.S./Essays on His Life & Work, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Articles about P.S./unpublished, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Articles about P.S., 1933, 1963, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Articles about P.S./published, 1938, 1945, 1973, 1982, 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Misc Corr (Paul Strand), 1922, 1932-1948, 1962, 1964, 1981, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Essays for Strand Book/Essays on His Life & Work, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Book Proposal/Strand Essay Book, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - PS to AS Misc Corr, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Virglio Tosi, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Milwaukee Museum Exhibitions/PS, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - MH/NR Correspondence, 1975-1976; cuid36370 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Articles by Naomi Rosenblum, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Strand Copy Prints for Dissertation/Rebecca, Mavin, Hartley, and Others, undated (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - Tempus Magazine (features photo by Paul Strand), 2014 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Automobile, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence about Paul Strand, 1962-1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Articles about PS after 1950, 1955, 1959, 1963, 1972-1976, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Baasch, K (friend of PS), 1933-1935 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - C - Conversation Notes PS, 1968, 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - D - Corres PS, 1964, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - E - Assorted Corresp PS, 1951-1952, 1955, 1960, 1963, 1969-1970, 1974-1975, 1977, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - F - Assorted Corrs PS, 1933, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - G - Corr Re: PS, 1954, 1958, 1960, 1975, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - I -Corresp Re: PS, 1975, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - J - Corr Re: PS, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - L - Corr Re: PS, 1966, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - M - Corr Re: PS, 1967, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - N - Corr Re: PS, 1968, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - O'Keeffe Re: PS, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Camera Club on NY Library, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Camera Club 1920 Strand (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Camera Info, 1901, 1905, 1914, 1965, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Clurman Harold Group Theatre Sykes (Strand), 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence on Strand, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Davidson, Basil Re: Strand, 1963, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Strand: ECS, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Exerpts: PS, 1916-1923, 1950-1953 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Greenwald, Dr. H. Jonathan & Dorothy, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Guggenheim/PS, 1940-1941, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - H - Corr with PS, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Dorothea Lange P.S. to D.L., undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - D.H. Lawrence Corr Re: Lady Chatterley's Lover (also neg of DH Lawrence), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - McCausland on PS (article by), undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Corr PS to WR Re: Medical Matters, 1973, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Marin Letters to PS, 1930-1932 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - P.S. Memorial, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Nancy Newall to P.S., 1947, 1949, 1950, 1953, 1956, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Dorothy Norman Re: P.S., 1965, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Jerome Melquist to P.S., 1933 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Re: Strand/Stieglitz, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Museum of Modern Art Comm. Advisory Xerox Re: Photography, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Mat Written by Others, Period of 1920-50, 1922, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Corr (extracts) to PS, 1965-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Conversation with PS about Painters: Stanton MacDonald Wright, Taos Painters, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Photographs List of, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Photos/R. Lazarus, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Photographs/Titles, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Machinery, Akeley Cam: Mach Photos PS, 1922, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Paul Strand, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Odds, Ends - Misc. Corresp PS, 1978, 1980-1981, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Original Rebecca Strand to PS, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - O'Keeffe Letters to NR incl permission Re: PS, 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Notes V Stevens Hazel Re: PS, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Misc Notes PS, 1963, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - List Ps Archive, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Films on Photographers, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Articles on Literature/20's, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Articles on Art/20's, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Photos Copy Prints for Dissertation, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Photography: Misc. Articles by PS, 1917, 1944-1946, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Photography Articles about PS, 1952, 1954, 1957, 1963, 1972, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Photography Commercial, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Purchases & Gifts, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photography Notices of talks given by PS, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Photography: Heartfield, Man Ray, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Photography, Recognition of, prices, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Photography: Fifth St. Backyard Photos, 1975; cuid36371 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Photography - Californians, Western, etc, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Photography: Documentary Hine, RIIS, FSA, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Photography: Influence on Young Photographs, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Photography: Publishing Problems, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Political Ideas, 1967-1968, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Publications Time in New England, 1947, 1951-1952, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Quotes from Strand Articles, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Publications: La France du Profil, 1951, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Living Egypt, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Un Paese, 1955, 1967, 1975, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Ghana Book/Davidson, 1963, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Monograph, 1961, 1972, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - R - Correspondence, 1941, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Royal Photo Society, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Walter Rosenblum into Catalogue etc…, 1949, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Roumania, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Russian Project, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - S - Correspondence, 1966, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Sheeler Corres + Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Stieglitz/Strand, 1968, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Stieglitz/Strand Corr. Beincke, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Stevens, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Steigl Circle/Corresp/Bei, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Philip Stevenson, 1952-1960, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Stevenson, 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Strand/Aperture Publ, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Strand/Articles by, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Strand Book Essays + Etc…, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Strand Family Photos, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Rebecca Strand to PS, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Strand Materials at CCP, 1916, 1929, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Strand Personal Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gerald Sykes, 1931-1934 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - T - Corresp, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Tomkins on Strand New Porker, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Travels 1911 Trip, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Travels 1915 Trip, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Student Papers on PS, 1963, 1971, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Travels: Ghana, 1969, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Travels - France, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Travel: Ireland/O'Malley, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Travels: Soviet Union, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Travels: New England, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Travels: Egypt, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - USSR - Proposal for Publication, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Fotographia Magazine (article about Paul Strand), 2004 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Strand/Stieglitz Corr/Copies, 1920-1929, 1933, 1935, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Stetchon, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - W - Correspondence, 1940, 1947, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Walker Film/Strand, 1982, 1985, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Wanamaker, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - XYZ, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hebrides Book, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art Magazine (article about Paul Strand), 2014 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - P.S. Poems (copies), undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Family Letter/Strand Parents, 1911-1915, 1918-1943 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
  - Rebecca James to PS/Re: ECS, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Strand Inquiries Re: Official Papers, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - RJS to Paul Strand/Copies, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Corr Re: Camera Club of NY, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - RS to PS/Corr/Originals & Copies, 1921-1923 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - RS to PS/Corr/Copies, 1924-1925 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
  - RS to PS/Corr/Originals & Copies 1920s, 1926-1927 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Stand/James King Bio, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Notes Re: Technical Matters, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Strand/Greengard/Met MM/Hambourg, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - National Gallery of Art/Corr Re: PS, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - French American Review/Corr & Articles Re: PS, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Edward Weston to PS/Corr/Originals, 1939, 1948-1949 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Interview (Misc) PS, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - PS Chronology, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - PS Early Photographs, Notes, Articles, Xeroxes of Images, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Galerie Zur Stockeregg/Paul Strand/1990, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Lumiere Press/PS Article to Corr, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Itinerary in Hazel's Hand PS, 1958-1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Maison Europeanne de la Photographie/PS Exhibition, 1993, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Political Photog/Roosevelt Wall/PS, 1944, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - PS/AS/Article, 1983, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - PS/Article/GEH 1990 - Article Minolta Mirror, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - PS Bibliography, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - PS/Corr Re: Use of Photos, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - PS/Lecture/New England Photos, 1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - PS/Assorted Exhibitions USA, 1969, 1971, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - PS/Exhibitions/Europe, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - PS/Exhibition/Pompidou Centre/Paris, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - PS/Exhibition/National Portrait Gallery/London, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - MMA Exhibition List/PS, 1975, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - PS/Exhibitions/MoMA, 1945, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - PS/Retrospective Exhibitions/Phila Mu, 1972, 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - PS/Passports, 1958-1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - PS/Exhibition: The World on My Doorstep, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - PS/Miscellaneous, 1988, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Paul Strand Sharpless and Fine Arts Visitor, 2000 (Box 65, Vhs 556_0004)
  - Strand Stieglitz Correspondence, 1915-1928 (Box 25, Folder 11-12, Box 26, Folder 1-5)
  - Strand Stieglitz Correspondence, 1922-1923, 1927, 1931-1933 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Research Notebooks focused on Paul Strand, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lewis Hine Promotional Material, 1977, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Corresp. About Hine, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Urena/Hine, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hine/Survey Covers/Articles/Misc, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Hine - GEH Holdings, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Hine - Own Writing - Early Influence, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Corr Re: Hine Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Hine/Articles/About Child Labor/Teens/Letters, 1911-1920 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Columbia U, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Lectures about Lewis Hine, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Hine/Articles About Child Labor, 1936, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Hine - Hastings, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - To Paul Kellog, 1921, 1931, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - NCLC Report, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Hine Exhibition - Information for, Quotes etc., Labels Brooklyn Museum, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Hine/Photos at ECS/ECS Records & Correspondence, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - LWH & Paul King Correspondence, 1921, 1924, 1933-1937, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Hine/TVA, 1976, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Hine, Lewis/WPA/National Research Project/Holyoke, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Hine/Work Portraits, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Hine/Misc Activities, 1920-1930 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Hine/Men at Work/Various Articles on Men at Work during 1920s, 1932-1933 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Hine/Misc Correspondence to LWH/Re: photos, 1933-1934 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - About Hine + Hine Doc Materials, 1975-1979, 1984, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Hine/Misc Corres Re:, 1915, 1933-1934, 1976, 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Unknown - Reminisces about Hine, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Naomi Notes Re: Hine, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Hine/Travels, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Lecture on Hine, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Lewis Hine/Letters/Memoirs, 1919, 1933, 1938-1939, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Copies of Lewis Hine Writings & Journal of Homer Folks, 1921-1939 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Corr Re: Hine Antecedents, 1956, 1973, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Talks/Papers on Hine, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Hine/Pittsburgh Survey, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Hine/American Red Cross/United States, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Hine/Red Cross/Balkans/France/Belgium, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Hine/Review & Publicity/Of Retrospective Exhibition, 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Lewis Hine, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Hine/Corr Re: Photos for Retrospective, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Hine/Reviews of Exhibitions During His Life, 1920, 1931, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Hine/Bibliography, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Hine/NY State Barge Canal, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Hine/Illustrations in Books, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Hine: Related Articles, not specifically on Hine, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Hine/Photos Used in Various Contexts, 1941, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Naomi Article on Hine, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Hine Used in Articles, 1971, 1976-1978, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Hine Posters, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hine/Correspondence/Late 30's/Kellogg, 1933, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hine/Odds & Ends, 1932-1939, 1987, 1996, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - WWI - Sc. 8, 1919, 1931, 1940, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Hine - Corr Re: Exhibit (Brooklyn Museum), 1974-1976, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Hine Clippings, 1939-1941, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - LH Films - Visuals, Negs of Films Panels, 1910-1916 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Hine Biography, 1940, 1956, 1976-1977, 1997, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Hine Drawings, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Lewis Hine Construir una Nacion (Press Clippings), 2014 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Hine - Exhibition Brochure/China, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Lewis Hine - Promotional Exhibition Programs, 1977, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Research Articles about Child Labor & Lewis Hine, 1909-1911, 1916-1917 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Hine/Misc, 1989, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Hine/Correspondence/LWH-EMC, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Articles Abt Hine, 1913, 1920, 1933, 1938-1939, 1946, 1967-1968, 1970, 1975, 1977, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Hine/Time Exposures (and other similar), 1911-1915, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Hine/Stryker Corr, 1935-1940 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Hine/Transcripts Re: Child Labor, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Misc Exhibits Hine, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Perrier/Hine, 2002, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Hine/Material from 20s and 30s/Columbia U, 1933-1939, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Articles about Hine, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Hine/Misc Articles About/Catalogs About, 1980, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Hine/Talks, Papers about/N+WR, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Hine, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Getty Symposium - Fall 2001, Sept 14 (Rescheduled June 13-15, 2002), 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Hine/Burns, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - America & Lewis Hine/Doc Film, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Willis/Lecture/Emp State, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Aperture/Hine, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Hine: Xeroxes/Letters & Articles, 1984, 1986, 1991-1992, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Hine/Emp/Willis, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Salisbury State/MD/Hine, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Canada/Hine, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Hine/Chicago/U of I, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - NR Research Notebooks about Lewis Hine, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - A World History of Photography Press Clippings, 1984-1986, 1989, 1992, 1994, 2001, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Hine Photo Company (George Eastman House), 1970 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Magazines with articles about Lewis Hine, 1979, 1989, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Lewis Hine & the National Child Labor Committee, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Lewis Hine, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - El Salvador in the Eye of the Beholder (Travelling Museum), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Middlebury_Donadio, M. (Emmie), 1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Ken Light/Haury Smithsonian, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Queens College, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Chicago/Doc, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Akron: Photo Essays/Adams Hine Steiglitz/Bernhard, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - NYU, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Oakland/Heyman, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Chicago - Columbia College, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Nov 13, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Stuhlman/GEH/Fazal, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Cont Photog Update, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Corr Lindley/Haury, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Arles France/Desvergnes, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Cambridge Perspectives on Photography/B. Michaels, 1990, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - MacMillan Biblio, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Encyclopedia of New York, 1988, 1990, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Houston Fotofest, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Photo Collections: A-F, 1980, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Photo Collections: G-M, 1969, 1984, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Photo Collections: N-Z, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981, 1984, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Dictionary of Art Macmillan Texts, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Macmillan Corr, 1986-1990, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Bibliographies, 1966, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Boston Public Library, 1974, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - MoMA - 17th Dec, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - National Photography Institute Seminar, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Christies 2110 Education, 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota TV - Photography, 1995; cuid36372 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Hammer, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - ICP Letter, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Oakland Museum, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Timeline, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Richard Stockton College/SP, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Robertson Visit, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Iceland Publication, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Italy, 1997-1999 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Hertzman/Cox/Artist Portraits, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - CUNY-Essays, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Pultz, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - "The Garden of Photographic Delights and How It Grew" (Naomi Rosenblum), undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Getty Center Photo Archive, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Booklist, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Photography Lists, undated (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
  - Rome/Gubbio, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Corrections: A Hist of Women Photogs, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Lily Sverner, 1994, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Grace R, 1994-2011 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Ch. 11, 12, 13 revised (A World History of Photography), undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lazarus, 1976, 1979, 1981-1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Mother Jones, 1989, 1991, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - AHOWP Revisions/Research Material, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 3, Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Book - 5th ed AWHOP, 1995, 2007, 2017 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Corr, 2005, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Abbeville Revision, 1984, 1987-1988, 1994, 1997, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Women in Photography, 1995-1999, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Abbeville New Edition, 1995, 2006-2008 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - European Strand/Aperture, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Naomi Emita/Interview, 2015 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Naomi: Writings by Naomi Rosenblum, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - CRAF, 2017 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Naomi Lena Fritsch Interview, 2013-2014 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Naomi Correspondence, 2001, 2004-2005, 2010-2016 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Janice Mellman, 2017 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Posner, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Manuela - Hine Book, 2011, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Timeline Photography, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Colville/C.H. White/Erwin, 1994, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Lerner, AL/Aline, 1985, 1991, 1993, 1996-2004 (Box 37, Folder 21)